

# Kazim Hussain

Web Developer

# **About me**

Hi, I'm a Kazim Hussain. I have been working as a web developer since 2021. I am also working on Graphic Design and Data Entry. I have Experience working on HTML, CSS & and JavaScript respectively. My Expertise is in Web Development & Graphic Designing

#### **Contact Me**

- +923114890967
- 🕜 kazimofficial347@gmail.com
- Sirki Muhala, Street no 3, Okara

## **Expertise Skill**

- Nextjs 13
- Tailwind
- Video Editing
- Graphic Designing
- Microsoft 360
- Front-end Development

#### **Education**

- 2018-2020Matriculation of ComputerScience Teps School Okara
- 2020-2022ICS of Post Graduate CollageOkara

### **Work Experience**

- Senior Front-End Developer 2021-2022
  - 1 Year Experience in Front-End with Nextjs 13 & Tailwind
  - 6 Month Experience in HTML, CSS & JavaScript
- Senior Graphic Designer 2020-2022
  - 2 Year Experience in Graphic Designing
  - 6 Month Experience in Teaching